SHIVANANDA B

Associate Developer

📞 +919901077217 🔞 shivananda.b12345@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shivananda-b-aab781197/ Pengalurul



EXPERIENCE

Associate Developer

Mindset Experience India Private Limited

Company Description

- Entegris CMC integration Project(Aug 2022- Aug 2023)
- I worked as a Developer on an S/4 HANA Implementation Project focusing on Core ABAP, Adobe Forms, BADI, and Reports.
- Johnson screen-SQL-master Dev(ABAP ALV grid and file interface) (March 2024 - June 2024).
- Worked on Johnson screen project on File interfaces of material worked on 2 requirements from end to end using ALV grid and updated and created material using BAPI and also File Upload from Folders.
- Develop the automation using the SAP BTP-IRPA (Nov 2023- Jan 2023) for Inter challenge Innovation Challenge Conducted by Mindset.
- SAP DEMOJAM APP(Nutri.ai app) (SAP build apps, BPA,IRPA Work zone, RAP)(Aug 2023 to November 2023).
- Build a healthy food app for the Demojam demo conducted by SAP.
 This app contains all menu's and Al Chef is also there according to user requirements.
- Build my own SAP BTP BPA, IRPA Use -case- and Demonstrate in SITBLR 2024(Dec 2023-feb 2024)
- App Library Fiori/UI5, CAPM, Odata, Work zone, Gateway services (Oct 2021 - June 2022).
- In this project, we built a demo UI5 app that helps the customers interact with real applications instead of interacting with prototypes with creating OData services Using S/4 Hana.
- CHS SOL SAP Apps MS(ACM Module, ABAP, CDS, Odata service, RAP) (July 2024 - present).
- Here my role is Developer, and I am responsible for the Development, Designing, and testing of implementation and move to Quality.
- Border State-BTP Developer(Datasphere, BTP)(July 2024 to September 2024).
- Create a replication flow from s4Hand system to datasphere and modify data and send it to Azure.

TRAINING / COURSES

SAP Datasphere and SAC Analytical Cloud Training

2 -3 months Training By Company and Attend SAP Datasphere Workshop Training.

CDS Course Through Udemy

ABAP, ODATA, BAdi Course through Udemy

RAP Course Through Open

SUMMARY

Working as a SAP-certified Backend Developer and BTP | Fiori developer at Mindset Consulting. Worked as SAP consultant with 3 + years of experience in SAP Fiori/UI5 and SAP ABAP/OData on SAP NetWeaver, Adobe Forms ABAP on HANA, Restful ABAP in various SAP Technologies and SAP IRPA and sap Build apps and BPA Responsible for Development, designing & testing of implementation of SAP development.

SKILLS

Core ABAP	OData	ABAP RAP	
SD Module	MM Mod	ule	
Sap Build Apps SAP BTP			
BPA(Build Proce	ess Auto	mation)	
Forms (Smart fo	orms & A	dobe Forms)	
Reports (ALV Reports), BADI, BAPI			
SAP UI5 SAP Fiori			
SAP NetWeaver	SAF	BTP-Workzone	
SEGW Gateway	Data	Datasphere	
SAC Analytics	CDS	OOP ABAP	
SAP BTP -IRPA	S/4 H	S/4 Hana	
Fiori launchpad	SAP	SAP API	
SAP Cloud Platform			

LANGUAGES

English Proficient	••••
Kannada Native	••••

EDUCATION

BTech

Dayananda Sagar University

- Computer Science
- Bangalore, India

PUC

Bharthi Composite PU College

School

Shree Cham Sugar School

06/2003 - 04/2015 ♀ KM Doddi

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS



Develop the Nutri.ai app for the Demo jam event Conducted By SAP

Only 6 teams are shortlisted. We are the one in out of six. In Nov-



Win Inter challenge Innovation Challenge Conducted by Mindset

Develop the automation using the SAP BTP-IRPA In Jan 2023



WIN SAP Build Hackathon -2024

3 days hackathon in April Conduct by SAP



Speaker in SITBLR Feb-2024

Build my own SAP BTP BPA Use -case and Demonstrate in SITBLR 2024

CERTIFICATION

SAP Certified Citizen Developer Associate - SAP Build Low-code/No-code Applications and Automation(C_LCNC_02)

SAP Certified Development Associate - Programming in SAP S/4HANA for SAP NetWeaver ABAP Programmers(C_S4HDEV1909)

SAP Certified Development Associate -SAP BTP Extensions with SAP Cloud Application Programming Model(C_CPE_14)

SAP Certified Development Associate - SAP Fiori Application Developer (C_FIORDEV_22)